davidweekleyhomes.com 2012-11-17

# Privacy Policy - David Weekley Homes

Since 1976, David Weekley Homes has developed relationships with our Customers based on enhancing the lives of our Customers and acting with the utmost integrity. We're aware of the confidence you demonstrate when you provide us with personal information. The Privacy Notice below is posted to demonstrate our adherence to the practices you'll find common to the best websites online. We will treat your information with the same integrity and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history.

David Weekley Homes respects the privacy of every individual. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this Policy. Your e-mail address is obtained for internal purposes only (as they relate to marketing and sale of David Weekley Homes' properties) and will not knowingly be sold or shared with any unaffiliated third party.

**Information We Collect**

David Weekley Homes collects information and data to personalize and improve your use of our website(s). We gather the following types of information:

> Information you give us: David Weekley Homes collects any information which you enter on our website. This includes but is not limited to your name, mailing address, e-mail address and other data you provide during your registration at our site or when you provide personal data through various places on our site.
> 
> Information automatically collected by David Weekley Homes: Like most websites, whenever you visit our site(s) we use "cookies" to collect and store information about a visitor site experience. We collect and analyze:
> 
>   * The IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet
>   * Computer and connection information such as your browser type and version
>   * Connection type and speed
>   * IP geolocation
>   * Operating system and platform
>   * Confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you
>   * The URLs which lead you to and around our Web site including the date and time
>   * The pages you viewed or searched for
> 

Your browser allows you to reject cookies and software is available from third parties which will allow you to visit our Web site without providing this information. You are welcomed at our Web site if you use this software but there may be a reduction in functionality on some pages of our site.

In addition, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. If you send us e-mails, from time to time we may use information about your preferences and interests to send updates to you about services or properties of David Weekley Homes that may be of interest to you. The information you provide will also be utilized for market research purposes.

We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services to us such as sending e-mail, analyzing Customer lists and data, providing marketing assistance, or consulting services. These third parties will have limited access to only the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose.

We also may track your visits to our site(s) that are launched from emails sent to you by David Weekley Homes. In some cases, this information may be identified to us by your email address, which enables us to improve your site and email experiences by better understanding your preferences.

We contract with an outside service called Omniture to help us better understand your use of DavidWeekleyHomes.com and other web sites we may manage. The Omniture software places cookies on your computer to collect various kinds of information for us related to the use of our websites, so that we may continue to refine and improve the sites and better serve you. Omniture is not allowed to collect any credit card, user name or password information, nor are they allowed to use data that they collect for us for any other purpose. Additionally, Omniture is contractually required to maintain all the information collected for us in strict confidence. You may opt out of the Omniture information collection by visiting [Omniture’s Web site](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/2o7#optout).

**E-mail Opt-in**

Visitors to our site who submit contact requests 'opt-in' to receive email follow-ups from the appropriate Team Member(s). Visitors who subscribe to our Home Club or Realtor News newsletters are also ‘opting-in’ to receive email follow-ups from the appropriate Team Members.

At any time, you may unsubscribe or ‘opt-out’ from receiving further e-mails by clicking the “manage my subscriptions” link at the bottom of e-mail messages, or by forwarding the e-mail to dwh@dwhomes.com with the word “remove” in the subject line.

**Forward-to-a-Friend Functionality**

If you feel that information about David Weekley Homes could be useful for a third party you know (e.g. your friends or family members etc.), you may use the forward-to-a-friend functionality that is available on many of our e-mails. If you choose to use our this service to tell a friend about David Weekley Homes, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-ail inviting him or her to visit the site. Our e-mail marketing provider, ExactTarget, stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

**Sharing Your Information**

David Weekley Homes may disclose or exchange with others information you have provided to us if we believe that the law requires us to do so or if it is necessary to protect the safety, rights or property of David Weekley Homes, our affiliates or our users.

David Weekley Homes will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, theft, misuse or alteration of your personal information. David Weekley Homes selects our business partners by using many criteria, including perceived trustworthiness. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that may receive the information.

Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. For example, if we need to mail something to you, we must share your name and address with a fulfillment company. We limit such third parties in their access and use of your personal information.

We may provide some of your information to our independent sales agent to follow up with you in connection with materials or services you request and as a part of our mailings to prospective Customers.

**Web Links**

Our site includes links to other Web sites. Those sites may have different privacy policies. If you click on to another Web site, you may want to check the privacy policy of that site, which will usually (but not always) be posted on the web site. David Weekley Homes is not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites.

**Children’s Online Privacy Act**

The David Weekley Homes Website is directed to adults and is not intended for children under the age of 18. David Weekley Homes complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and does not permit registration by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Accuracy of Personal Information

We need your help in making sure your personal information is correct in our systems. Please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or email address You may correct your personal information or select the option not to receive future David Weekley Homes contacts (i.e. mailings, calls, etc.) by emailing webmaster@dwhomes.com.

**Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

**Changes to the Policy**

From time to time, we may find it necessary to revise our Privacy Policy. We will post these changes on this page, and/or update the Modification Date below.

**Last Modified Date**

This Privacy Policy was last modified on October 5, 2009.

**Contacting David Weekley Homes**

If you have any questions regarding this policy you may contact us by using the contact information that follows.  
By Postal Mail:  
David Weekley Homes  
1111 N. Post Oak Rd  
Houston, Texas 77055
